Contact

michelelott@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/michele-garrett-lott-49961b101 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Healthcare Management
Patient Safety

Languages English

Michele Garrett/Lott

Travel RN at Travel

Fort Worth, Texas

Summary

Experienced Ortho/ Rehabilitation Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the Med Surg, skilled unit & health care industry. Strong healthcare services professional skilled in Electronic Medical Record (EMR), Nursing, Healthcare Management, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR).

Experience

Medical Solutions
Travel RN
October 2019 - Present (10 months)
Fort Worth, Texas

Sacred Heart Health System
RN, Unit Manager Rehab
July 2014 - September 2019 (5 years 3 months)

Education

Pensacola State College
Associate of Science (AS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2006 - 2012)